Enas awad sello

■ enas.awad169@gmail.com☐ Enas-Sello

My web stie



Work Experience

Freelancer (20201 till now)

- User Experience Designer
- Frontend Developer

AAIB front end React.js (March 2022 - August 2022)

- · User Experience Designer using figma
- Frontend Developer using React

Markting

- Admin for clothing salles group in Egypt and Saudi Arsbia at facbook(2021 till now)
- American Council in Mansoura for several courses (2021)

Internships

ITI/AAIB Academy Internships (March 2022 - August 2022)

- mern | mean devlopment track ,information Technology Instituté (ITI), Arab African International Bank (AAIB) web Desgin
- Google growth UX Design Professional (2021 2022)

Proiects

Amazon-clone: worked on E-commerce like amazone using React & Redux and node

Github: BackEnd, FrontEnd, Demo

Movie App: worked on movie website like Netflix using React & Redux & fakeApi

Github : Repo

Admin Dashbord: worked on E-commerce Dashbord using React & Redux and node

Github: BackEnd, FrontEnd

Chat App: worked on chat app using HTML & Css & node & sokit.io

Github: Repo

Landing page: worked on Landing page using React & Sass

Github : Repo

Profile

I graduated from Al-Azher university , studied three diplomas in teaching and psychological health disabilities section . worked as an Arabic teacher for deaf and speechless .

I have started my career in web devlopment with FWD frond-end track by the end of 2020 after that

I started UX design process in 2021 with google and coursera " Google UX Design Professional "

and finally I joined ITI (information technology institute) MERN Stack .

skills

Frontend Technologies

- Html 5
- · Css 3 (bootstrap, tailwind)
- javaScript
- ECMAScript
- React
- React Native

Back-end Technologies

- Node js
- express js
- Nest.js

Other Technologies

- MongoDB
- Firebase
- SQL database
- git&github
- UI/UX designing tools [Figma, Adobe XD]

Education

Psychological health Dibloma

- · Psychological health of disabilities (2019 2020) Kafr El-sheikh University
- Abnormal physiology (2018 2019) Mansoura University

General Diploma in Education

· Arabic teaching Diploma (2017 - 2018)

alahzer university

arabic and islamic studies for girl, Islamic Studies Department (2013-2017)

languages

Arabic : Native English : good